Peter Fallon - Gallery Press collection, circa 1967-1998
Emory University
- Literary manuscripts, 1969-1998, Series 1; Boxes 1-111
  - Gallery Press submission files, ca. 1966-1997, Subseries 1.2; Boxes 87-99
    - Sheridan, Peter (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Teevan, Colin (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Teevan, Colin (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Ward, H.G. (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Wilkinson, Susan (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Williams, T.E.O. (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - n.d. (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - n.d. (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - n.d. (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Illustration Submission
    - McCannon, Desdemona (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Deerfield Press author files, Subseries 1.3; Box 100
    - John O'Brien correspondence (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Berry, Wendell (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Boland, Eavan (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Creeley, Robert (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Deerfield Press Logo (Box OP56)
    - Dickey, James (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Dickey, James, Scion, artwork (Box OP57)
    - Engelland, Timothy (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Hall, Donald (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Kinnell, Galway (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Kinsella, Thomas (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - The Little Brown House: A Garland for Robert McGlynn, artwork (Box OP58)
    - The Little Brown House: A Garland for Robert McGlynn, correspondence 1983-1984 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - The Little Brown House: A Garland for Robert McGlynn, MS and TS (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - The Little Brown House: A Garland for Robert McGlynn, misc. (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Mahon, Derek (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Merrill, James (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Muldoon, Paul (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Ó Díreáin, Máirtín (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Ó Díreáin, Máirtín, Four Poems (back page only) (Box OP59)
    - Seay, James (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Wilbur, Richard (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - O'Brien Press author files, 1980-1985, Subseries 1.4; Boxes 101-109
    - Behan, Brendan (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Behan, Brendan (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Behan, Brendan (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Behan, Brendan (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Behan, Brendan, After the Wake (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Boyle, Patrick (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Friel, Brian (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Jordan, Neil (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Kinsella, Thomas (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Leland, Jeremy (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Leland, Jeremy (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Leland, Jeremy, The Last Sandcastle, Proof with corrections (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Leland, Jeremy, The Last Sandcastle, Proof with corrections (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Leland, Jeremy, The Last Sandcastle, TS with corrections (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Mac an tSaoi, Máire, "Inquisito 1584," "No Compromise," "Finit," "For Sheila" (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Mac Liammóir, Micheal (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - McCarthy, Thomas (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, correspondence (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 1-100 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 101-200 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 201-300 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 301-375 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 1-100 (photocopy) (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 101-200 (photocopy) (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 201-300 (photocopy) (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS, p. 301-375 (photocopy) (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Ó Cadhain, Máirtín, Churchyard Clay, TS (incomplete) (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - O'Connor, John (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - O'Donnell, Peadar, "The Big Windows" (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Ó Faoláin, Seán, "What It Feels Like to Be a Writer" (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - O'Grady, Desmond - "These Fields in Springtime" (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - O'Kelly, Seamus (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - O'Kelly, Seamus, The Weaver's Grave (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - O'Kelly, Seamus, The Weaver's Grave (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Ó Siadhail, Mícheál (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Ó Siochfhradha, Pádraig, Jimeen [Patricia Egan, Peter Fallon, and Íde ní Laoghaire, translators] (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Paulin, Tom (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Ryan, Richard, TS poems (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - West, Anthony C. (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - West, Anthony C., The Casual Comedy, MS (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - West, Anthony C., The Casual Comedy, MS (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - West, Anthony C., The Casual Comedy, MS (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - West, Anthony C., The Casual Comedy, MS (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - West, Anthony C., The Casual Comedy, MS (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - West, Anthony C., The Casual Comedy, MS (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Subject Files
    - Advertisements (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Allison and Busby correspondence (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Artwork (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - O'Brien Press Artwork (Box OP60)
    - The Best from the Bell Plans (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Book Fairs (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Catalogue, Spring 1984 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Cle (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Cle (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - "Comps, etc..." (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Dolmen Press Correspondence (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Frankfurt Report (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - "Information in..." (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Lenister Leader Ltd. (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Lenister Leader Ltd. (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - The Lucky Bag (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - The Lucky Bag (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - The Lucky Bag (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - The Lucky Bag (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - The Lucky Bag (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - The Lucky Bag (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - The Lucky Bag (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - The Lucky Bag; In the Long Ago (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Lullabies (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Lullabies (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Magazine Solicitation Research Notes (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Munster Writers' Co-Operative Correspondence (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Permissions (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - Printed material (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Promotional material (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Reviews (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - Royalties (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - Submissions correspondence (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Submissions correspondence (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Submissions Correspondence (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Submissions Correspondence (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Submissions Correspondence (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Submissions Correspondence (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - St. Vincent DePaul (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Oldcastle Enterprises/After Hours Books author files, Subseries 1.5; Boxes 110-111
    - Fallon, Peter, Laurence Gilson and the Gilson Endowed School, Oldcastle (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - McMann, Jean, Correspondence (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - McMann, Jean, "Loughcrew: form, History and meaning in an Irish Megalithic Landscape" (Ph.D. dissertation, UC Berkeley, 1991) (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - McMann, Jean, Loughcrew: The Cairns - A Guide, Halftone (Box OP61)
    - McMann, Jean, Loughcrew: The Cairns - A Guide, MS with corrections (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - McMann, Jean, Loughcrew: The Cairns - A Guide, Miscellaneous (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - McMann, Jean, Loughcrew: The Cairns - A Guide, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - McMann, Jean, Loughcrew: The Cairns - A Guide, Mock-ups with corrections (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Moynagh, Peter, Correspondence (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Moynagh, Peter, TS poems (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Moynagh, Peter, Peter Moynagh - A Life, Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Moynagh, Peter, Peter Moynagh - A Life, Mock-ups (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Moynagh, Peter, Peter Moynagh - A Life, TS with corrections (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Oldcastle Enterprises and After Hours Books, Miscellaneous (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, ca. 1967-1998, Series 2; Boxes 112-144
  The Peter Fallon, Gallery Press collection contain extensive files of correspondence spanning 1968-1998. The largest part of this correspondence is located in Series 2, though most correspondence directly related to books published by the Gallery Press is located in subseries 1.1; submissions correspondence may also be located in subseries 1.2; some correspondence related to Deerfield Press, O'Brien Press, and Oldcastle Enterprises and After Hours Books is located in subseries 1.3, 1.4, and 1.5, respectively; correspondence related to works edited by Peter Fallon is generally located in subseries 3.2; and letters regarding Fallon's lecture tours of the United States and Japan are ordinarily located in subseries 3.3. Peter Fallon generally filed his correspondence according to subject such as "correspondence" or "Business correspondence" although he maintained alphabatized files for letters from friends, colleagues, and dignitaries.
  This series attempts to maintain these systems of filing. Therefore, subseries 2.1 contains general correspondence organized by date. This correspondence includes fan mail as well as correspondence with friends, literary and artistic figures, and business contacts (including other publishers). Subseries 2.2 contains correspondence that is alphabetically arranged. While the majority of this is personal correspondence between Fallon and other writers and musicians, some of this correspondence is related to works that Fallon edited for Gallery or other presses. There are also a very few submissions. Please note that all correspondence with Seamus Heaney, including personal correspondence, is restricted and is located in box 86 of subseries 1.1. Business correspondence.
  Organized into three subseries: (2.1) General correspondence, (2.2) Literary correspondence, and (2.3) Business correspondence.
  Restrictions on access
  Special restrictions apply: Subseries 2.2., Letters by Seamus Heaney are closed to researchers.
  - General correspondence, 1968-1998, Subseries 2.1; Boxes 112-123
    Arranged in chronological order.
    - Correspondence, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Early 1970s (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, Early 1970s (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards, Early 1970s (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970s (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Nov 1970 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Dec 1970 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Greeting Card, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Invitations, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Mar 1971 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Apr-Aug1971 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1971 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1971, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Aug 1972 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Sep-Dec 1972 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Dec 1973 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1973, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Greeting Cards, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1974 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1974 (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1974, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1974 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Greeting Cards, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Invitations, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Dec 1976 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1976, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan -Dec 1977 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1977, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Invitations, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1978 (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1978 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1978, n.d. (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Greeting Cards, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978 (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Invitations, 1979 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, 1980 (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Greeting Cards, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Invitations, 1981 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Greeting Card, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Invitation, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1982 (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Greeting Cards, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Invitations, 1983 (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Greeting Cards, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1984 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jan-May 1985 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Jun-Dec 1985 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1985, n.d. (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, 1985 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Greeting Cards, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Invitations, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Invitations, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1987 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Invitations, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1988 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Jan- Dec 1989 (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1989, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Invitations, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1989 (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Jun 1990 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Jul-Dec 1990 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1990, n.d. (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Greeting Cards, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Invitations, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Dec 1991 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1991, n.d. (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Greeting Cards, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Invitations, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1991 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Greeting Cards, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Invitations, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1992 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Greeting Cards, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Invitations, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1993 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Greeting Cards, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1994 (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jan-Apr 1995 (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, May-Dec 1995 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1995, n.d. (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Greeting Cards, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Invitations, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Greeting Cards, 1996-1998 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Invitations, 1996-1998 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - Invitations, 1996-1998 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Greeting Cards, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Invitations, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, n.d. (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Literary correspondence, ca. 1967-1997, Subseries 2.2; Boxes 124-128
    Arranged in alphabetical order, with restricted correspondence at the end.
    - Agee, Chris, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Ashberry, John, 1981 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Asikoff, Louis, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Atwood, Margaret, 1995-1996 (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Auden, W.H., ca. 1972 (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Ballagh, Robert, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Banville, Janet, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Banville, John, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Barks, Coleman, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Barnes, John, 1987 (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Barry, Sebastian, 1980-1982 (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Basic, Viv, 1976; n.d. (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Beattie, Ann, 1996; n.d. (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Beckett, Samuel, 1979-1983 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Behan, John, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Bernan, Bob, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 16)
    - Berry, Wendell, 1979-1994, with TS "The Wild Birds" (Box 124, Folder 17)
    - Bincy, Maeve, 1997 (Box 124, Folder 18)
    - Bolan, Marc, 1972 (Box 124, Folder 19)
    - Boland, Eavan, 1978-1986 (Box 124, Folder 20)
    - Boland, Rosita, 1983-1994 (Box 124, Folder 21)
    - Bolger, Dermot, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 22)
    - Boran, Pat, 1988-1990 (Box 124, Folder 23)
    - Bowle, Brian, 1984 (Box 124, Folder 24)
    - Boyle Patrick, 1981 (Box 124, Folder 25)
    - Brandt, Ruth, 1980 (Box 124, Folder 26)
    - Brennan, Rory, 1978-1985 (Box 124, Folder 27)
    - Brown, Pete, ca. 1972 (Box 124, Folder 28)
    - Burns, Jim, 1969-1971 (Box 124, Folder 29)
    - Byron, Catherine, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 30)
    - Cafferky, Tony, 1971-1981 (Box 124, Folder 31)
    - Carr, Eamon, 1969-1972, with TS poems (Box 124, Folder 32)
    - Carver, Ray, 1986 (Box 124, Folder 33)
    - Casey, Philip, 1970-1995 (Box 124, Folder 34)
    - Cassidy, Laurence, 1995 (Box 124, Folder 35)
    - Clark, Sean, 1986-1988 (Box 124, Folder 36)
    - Coady, Michael, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 37)
    - Connolly, Susan, 1997, with submissions (Box 124, Folder 38)
    - Connors, Bruton, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 39)
    - Conway, Anne-Marie, 1983 (Box 124, Folder 40)
    - Cooke, Barrie, 1989-1992 (Box 124, Folder 41)
    - Costello, Elvis, n.d. (Box 124, Folder 42)
    - Coughlin, Jack, 1980-1993 (Box 124, Folder 43)
    - Cunliffe, Dave, 1969 (Box 124, Folder 44)
    - Daly, Padraig, 1975 (Box 124, Folder 45)
    - Davitt, Michael, 1990 (Box 124, Folder 46)
    - Dawe, Gerald, 1987-1995 (Box 124, Folder 47)
    - Deane, John F, 1972-1990s (Box 124, Folder 48)
    - Delanty, Greg, 1982-1991 (Box 124, Folder 49)
    - Devlin, Polly, 1985 (Box 124, Folder 50)
    - Dickey, James, 1980-1990 (Box 124, Folder 51)
    - Donaghue, Denis, 1974 (Box 124, Folder 52)
    - Donleavy, J.P., 1981 (Box 124, Folder 53)
    - Donlon, Pat, 1990s (Box 124, Folder 54)
    - Donnelly, Neil, 1980-1995 (Box 124, Folder 55)
    - Donovan, Gerard, 1991 (Box 124, Folder 56)
    - Dorfman, Ariel, 1995-1997 (Box 124, Folder 57)
    - Dorgan, Theo, 1981-1992 (Box 124, Folder 58)
    - Dunn, Stephen, 1996 (Box 124, Folder 59)
    - Dunne, Seán, 1975-1992, with TS poem (Box 124, Folder 60)
    - Durcan, Paul, 1992-1994 (Box 124, Folder 61)
    - Egan, Desmond, 1971-1973 (Box 124, Folder 62)
    - Ennis, John, 1994-1997 (Box 124, Folder 63)
    - Faller, Kevin, 1978 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Fallon, Bernard (B.P.), 1969-1995, with TS and MS essay (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Fennell, Nuala, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Fitzmaurice, Gabriel, 1987-1997 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Foley, Mike, 1983 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Forché, Carolyn, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Gall, Martin, 1987-1989 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Gallagher, Tess, 1976-1994 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Galvin, Patrick, 1970-1978 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Gardner, Donald, 1969 (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Gascoyne, David, n.d., [TS poem sent to Katherine Kavanagh] (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Gibbon, Monk, 1983 (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1970-1973 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Glavin, Anthony, 1980-1997 (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Gonne, Maud, 1939-1943 includes newspaper clippings (letters addressed to Donal Griffin and sent to Fallon) (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Greally, Hanna, 1975 (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Grennan, Eamon, 1976-1982 (Box 125, Folder 17)
    - Haines, John, 1983-1984 (Box 125, Folder 18)
    - Hall, Donald, 1976-1991 (Box 125, Folder 19)
    - Halpin, Mary, 1982 (Box 125, Folder 20)
    - Hammond, David, 1980 (Box 125, Folder 21)
    - Harding, Michael, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 22)
    - Harmon, Maurice, 1978-1997 (Box 125, Folder 23)
    - Hartnett, Micheal, 1990 (Box 125, Folder 24)
    - Harvey, Frank, 1977-1981 (Box 125, Folder 25)
    - Hayes, Aidan, 1992-1993 (Box 125, Folder 26)
    - Healy, Dermot, 1994; n.d. (Box 125, Folder 27)
    - Heaney, Seamus, 1985-1995 [See Restricted Correspondence: Box 128a] (Box -, Folder -)
    - Hedin, Robert, 1983-1987 (Box 125, Folder 28)
    - Heighton, Steve, 1997 (Box 125, Folder 29)
    - Henri, Adrian, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 30)
    - Hewitt, John, 1972-1984, with TS poems (Box 125, Folder 31)
    - Higgins, Aidan, 1979-1987, with TS essays (Box 125, Folder 32)
    - Hill, Derek, 1985 (Box 125, Folder 33)
    - Hobsbaum, Philip, 1977 (Box 125, Folder 34)
    - Hogan, Des, 1976 (Box 125, Folder 35)
    - Horovitz, Michael, 1971-1993 (Box 125, Folder 36)
    - Hughes, Carol, 1973 (Box 125, Folder 37)
    - Hughes, Olwyn, 1969 (Box 125, Folder 38)
    - Hughes, Ted, 1974-1996 (Box 125, Folder 39)
    - Isley, Alexandra, 1983 (Box 125, Folder 40)
    - Jackson, Alan, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 41)
    - Johnston, Jennifer, 1981-1983 (Box 125, Folder 42)
    - Johnstone, Robert, 1970-1971 (Box 125, Folder 43)
    - Jordan, Neil, n.d. (Box 125, Folder 44)
    - Kane, Michael, 1977-1991 (Box 125, Folder 45)
    - Kavanagh, Patrick, 1967-1986, with Ted Hughes letter, 1967 (Box 125, Folder 46)
    - Keane, John B., 1985-1990 (Box 125, Folder 47)
    - Kearney, Richard, 1983-1987 (Box 125, Folder 48)
    - Kennelly, Brendan, 1991-1997 (Box 125, Folder 49)
    - Kiely, Benedict, ca 1980-1985 (Box 125, Folder 50)
    - Kilroy, Thomas, 1992-1994 (Box 125, Folder 51)
    - Kinsella, Thomas, 1972-1995 (Box 125, Folder 52)
    - Kumin, Maxine, 1987-1991 (Box 125, Folder 53)
    - Lalor, Brian, 1970-1981 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Lavin, Mary, 1979-1985, with TS prose (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Le Brocquy, Louis, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Liddy, James, n.d. (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Logue, Christopher, 1980 (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Lucy, Sean, 1975-1983 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Lynch, Brian, 1973-1976 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Lynott, Philip, 1970s, with MS and TS about Lynott and Peter Fallon, 1974 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - McBreen, Joan, 1997 (Box 126, Folder 9)
    - McCarthy, Justin, 1990-1992 (Box 126, Folder 10)
    - McCarthy, Thomas, ca. 1976-1984 (Box 126, Folder 11)
    - McComack, Bill, 1982-1983 (Box 126, Folder 12)
    - McFadden, Roy, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - McGahern, John, 1977-1991 (Box 126, Folder 14)